ACOF

Finally some real news! Robert has posted an update at the official site, though it isn't in the news section: 
drippinginfromthenewsposts...
11/16/2005 1:45:23 PM - by CURE:ROBERT

SO!
WHY NO NEWS POSTS?
BECAUSE THERE IS NO REAL NEWS AS SUCH TO POST?
I AM WRAPPING UP THE NEXT RE-ISSUES WITH VARIOUS PEOPLE - THE BLUE SUNSHINE, TOP, THOTD AND KMKMKM DELUXE EDITIONS - COMPILING EXTRAS CD'S, REMASTERING THE SOUND, FIXING THE BOOKLETS UP...
ALL SCHEDULED FOR RELEASE IN SPRING 2006...
WRITING SOME FILM MUSIC...
CHOOSING THE BEST DEMOS...
GETTING THE WORDS RIGHT...
PUTTING TOGETHER A 5.1 LIVE SUMMER 2005 DVD THING...
LIVING...
WE WILL NOW NOT BE IN THE STUDIO 'FOR REAL' UNTIL JANUARY 2006...
BUT WE ARE STILL ON COURSE FOR A SUMMER RELEASE AS IT'S ALL IN THE PREPARATION!
LATER...
LOVE
ROBERT
PS
THE REASON WE ARE NOT ON THE LIVE8 DVD IS BECAUSE 'THEY' WANTED 'HITS'... PLUS CA CHANGE, PLUS C'EST LA MEME CHOSE? OR SOMETHING...



And some info from HispaCure and Universal Music Spain: 

"This is Ivan from hispaCure Fan Club Spain.
 
Last week we spoke with some people from UNIVERSAL MUSIC SPAIN. They told us some news-rumors about The Cure in 2006:
 
- New album and New Tour (spring 2006). Robert told us in our meeting with the band after Benicassim Concert. He also announced it during the 
press conference at this festival.
 
- First Quarter 2006 (january - march): They will release the new remaster deluxe editions. UNIVERSAL MUSIC SPAIN told us that they only 
have news about THE HEAD ON THE DOOR remaster album ... but they also suppose that it will be also two more delux editions.
 
- First Quarter 2006 (january - march): The Cure will release IN ORANGE DVD !!
 
This is the info UNIVERSAL MUSIC SPAIN had one week ago, they also told us that they are not sure about the correct dates these items will be 
released."
 




The Cure to hit studio in January Friday November 18, 02:02 AM     
Click to enlarge photo  
 
 
TORONTO (Billboard) - The Cure plans to hit the studio in January to record its next album, according to a post from frontman Robert Smith on the group's Web site (http://www.thecure.com).

"We are still on course for a summer release, as it's all in the preparation," he said.

The-as-yet-untitled effort will be the Cure's first since keyboardist Roger O'Donnell and guitarist Perry Bamonte left the band earlier this year (former guitarist Porl Thompson has since rejoined). It will be the follow-up to 2004's "The Cure," which has sold 317,000 copies in the United States, according to Nielsen SoundScan.

Smith also said that he is close to completing the next phase of the band's expanded reissue series, which will include 1984's "The Top," 1985's "The Head on the Door" and 1987's "Kiss Me Kiss Me Kiss Me, as well as "The Blue Sunshine," a 1983 album Smith and Steve Severin, the guitarist with Siouxsie and the Banshees, created under the name the Glove. The sets should be out by next spring.

In addition, Smith is assembling a live DVD from the Cure's summer performances and "writing some film music," according to his message.

Reuters/Billboard

